{
"questions":[{
    "question": "Who invented the C++ programming language?",
    "answers" : [{
        "a" : "Arthur O'Dwyer",
        "b" : "Rodger Cadenhead",
        "c" : "Jessie Letherhead",
        "d" : "Bjarne Stroustrup"
    }],
    "correct" : "d"
},
{"question": "Bootstrap was invented by what socail neworking company?",

    "answers" : [{
        "a" : "Facebook",
        "b" : "Snapchat",
        "c" : "Twitter",
        "d" : "Linkedin"
    }],
    "correct": "c"
    },
{
"question": "Who invented the Three.js?",
"answers" : [{
    "a" : "Kevin Macleod",
    "b" : "Ricardo Cabello",
    "c" : "Soledad Penadés",
    "d" : "Brendan Eich"
}],

"correct" : "b"
},
{
    "question": "Rosenbrock function are associated with which shape?",
    "answers" : [{
        "a" : "Bowl",
        "b" : "Bell",
        "c" : "Sphere",
        "d" : "Bannana"
    }],
    "correct": "d"
},

{"question": "If (7e + 5)/e = 26/3, then the value of 'e' is?",

    "answers" : [{
        "a" : "5",
        "b" : "7",
        "c" : "3",
        "d" : "4"
    }],
    "correct": "c"
    },

{"question": "Which algebra specification implements associativity law",

"answers" : [{
    "a" : "Setoids",
    "b" : "Semigroups",
    "c" : "Monoids",
    "d" : "Functors"
}],
"correct": "b"
}
,
{"question": "Which Theorem can be used to reverse conditional probabilites",

"answers" : [{
    "a" : "Bayes Theorem",
    "b" : "Central Limit Theorem",
    "c" : "Cramers Theorem",
    "d" : "Jackson Theorem"
}],
"correct": "a"
}
,

    {"question": "Who is coined the CQRS pattern?",

        "answers" : [{
            "a" : "Cris Sawyer",
            "b" : "Greg Young",
            "c" : "Dan Bunten",
            "d" : "Tim Schafer"
        }],
        "correct": "b"
        },
        {"question": "A category is said to be of what type?",

            "answers" : [{
                "a" : "Disjoint",
                "b" : "Intersection",
                "c" : "Aggregated",
                "d" : "Union"
            }],
            "correct": "d"
            },
            

        {"question": "Who published the first book the first book on recreational mathematics, Problèmes Plaisants in 1612",

            "answers" : [{
                "a" : "Descartes",
                "b" : "De Morgan",
                "c" : "Euler",
                "d" : "Bachet"
            }],
            "correct": "d"
            }
    

]

}